<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyHostel</string>
    <string name="about_us"><b>Hostel Management App</b>\n\n
        <i>Developed by:\nChandana (4MW20CS018)</i>\n<i>Dhrishya (4MW20CS026)</i>\n\n<i>Submitted to:\nMs.SAHANA Karanth, Senior Assistant Professor, CSE, SMVITM</i>\n
        \nAn Android application for hostel management offers several advantages for both hostel owners and residents.\n\n<b>Here are some specific benefits:</b>\n
        \n<b>Simplified Management:</b> \n\n A hostel management Android app streamlines and automates various management tasks.
        This simplifies the overall management process, saves time, and reduces the likelihood of errors.
        \n\n<b>Real-Time Notifications:</b> The Android app can send real-time notifications to both hostel management and residents.
        Important updates, such as booking confirmations, check-in/check-out reminders, maintenance schedules, or emergency alerts, can be instantly communicated through the app, ensuring timely information dissemination. \n\n
        <b>Seamless Communication:</b> The app facilitates smooth communication between hostel management and residents. Residents can use the app to submit requests, report issues, or seek assistance.
        Hostel management can efficiently address these inquiries and communicate updates or resolutions directly through the app.\n\n
        <b>Resource Management:</b> The app can help manage hostel resources effectively. Hostel staff can track inventory, manage supplies,
        and monitor usage through the app. This ensures that essential items like linens, toiletries, or kitchen supplies are adequately stocked and minimizes wastage. \n\n
        <b>Analytics and Reporting:</b> The app can generate comprehensive reports and analytics regarding various aspects of hostel operations, including occupancy rates, revenue, guest feedback,
        and maintenance requests. These insights enable hostel owners to make data-driven decisions, identify trends, and improve overall performance.\n\n
        <b>Mobility and Accessibility:</b> By being accessible on Android devices, the app offers mobility and convenience to both hostel management and residents. They can access the apps features and
        functionalities from anywhere, anytime, facilitating efficient management and improved resident experience.
     </string>

    <!-- Checkout activity -->
    <string name="title_activity_checkout">CheckoutActivity</string>
    <string name="checkout_item_description">Description</string>
    <string name="googlepay_status_unavailable" translatable="false">Unfortunately, Google Pay is
        not available on this phone.
    </string>
    <string name="payments_show_name" translatable="false">Successfully received payment data for
        %s!
    </string>
</resources>